Guide to the Ambassador Auditorium Collection ARS.0043
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Series 10: Concert Recordings, 252 boxes (266.2 linear ft.)
  - Audio Open Reel Tapes and Cassettes
    - Concert Recordings:, 05-07-1984 -- 12-04-1984; 36 audio cassettes (Box 668)
      10-28-1984: [1 cassette, labeled “Tape 2”] The Best of Gilbert and Sullivan with the Stars of the D’Oyly Carte Opera Company; Kenneth Sandford, bass-baritone; Vivian Tierney, soprano; Lorraine Daniels, mezzo-soprano; Geoffrey Shovelton, tenor; Alistair Donkin, baritone; David Mackie, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8444:1-2), Box 533]
      11-03-1984: Pilar Lorengar, soprano; Jeffrey Goldberg, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8445:1-2), Box 533]
      11-08-1984: [2 cassettes] Guarneri String Quartet: [for program information, see Tapes (8448:1-2), Box 534]
      11-10-1984: Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra; Gerard Schwarz, director; Daniel Lewis, guest conductor; Paul Shure, violin: Britten, Benjamin, 1913-1976. Variations on a theme of Frank Bridge -- Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Concertos, violin, string orchestra, H. VIIa, 1, C major -- Voříšek, Jan Hugo, 1791-1825. Symphony, D major
      11-13-1984: [2 cassettes] Orchestra of the 18th Century; Frans Brueggen, director/conductor: [for program information, see Tapes (8450:1-2), Box 534]
      11-15-1984: Judith Blegen, soprano; Håkan Hagegård, baritone; Martin Katz, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8451:1-2), Box 534]
      11-28-1984: Don Shirley Trio: [for program information, see Tapes (8453:1-2), Box 534]
      11-29-1984: Kwansei Gakuin University Symphony Band: [for program information, see Tapes (8455:1-2), Box 534]
      12-01-1984: [2 cassettes] Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra (L.A.C.O.); Gerard Schwarz, director/conductor; Zara Nelsova, cello: Sibelius, Jean, 1865-1957. Belsazars gästabud. Suite -- Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Concertos, violoncello, orchestra, no. 1, op. 33, A minor -- Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Symphonies, H. I, 103, E♭ major
      12-02-1984: [2 cassettes] Klezmorim: [no program listed; see also Tapes (8456:1-2), Boxes 534 and 535]
      12-04-1984: A Salute to Swing; Benny Carter, alto saxophone/clarinet; Hank Jones [replaced Teddy Wilson, who was ill], piano; Remo Palmier, guitar; Red Norvo, vibraphone; Louie Bellson, drums; George Duvivier, bass: [for program information, see Tapes (8457:1-2), Box 535]
      Young Musicians Foundation. Debut Orchestra; American Youth Symphony; Stulberg, Neal; Mehta, Mehli; Jaffe, Claudio; Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra; Schwarz, Gerard; Sitkovetsky, Dmitry; Statsradiofoniens symfoniorkester (Copenhagen, Denmark); Ehrling, Sixten; McDuffie, Robert; Vogel, Allan; Mabee, Patricia; Davis, Douglas; Shostac, David; Lakatos, Janet; Talvi, Ilkka; Morich, Dale; Phillips-Thornburgh, Maurita; Pasadena Chamber Orchestra; Auer, Edward; Beaux Arts Trio; Duerr, Robert; Jeffryes, Jai; Salerno-Sonnenberg, Nadja; Oppens, Ursula; Sabicas; Shovelton, Geoffrey; Mackie, David; Tierney, Vivian; Donkin, Alistair; Ameling, Elly; Daniels, Lorraine; Sandford, Kenneth; D'Oyly Carte Opera Company; Lewis, Daniel; Shure, Paul; Pludermacher, Georges; Guarneri Quartet; Lorengar, Pilar; Goldberg, Jeffrey; Fernández, Eduardo; Kovacevich, Stephen; Katz, Martin; Hagegård, Håkan; Richman, James; Miller, Sandra; Brüggen, Frans; Milstein, Nathan; Blegen, Judith; Orchestra of the 18th Century; Don Shirley Trio; Nelsova, Zara; Carter, Benny; Klezmorim; Concert Royal (Musical group: U.S.); New York Baroque Dance Company; Turocy, Catherine; Shirley, Don; Bellson, Louis; Norvo, Red; Palmier, Remo; Jones, Hank; Duvivier, George
    - Concert Recordings:, 12-05-1984 -- 03-23-1985; 36 audio cassettes (Box 669)
      12-05-1984: [2 cassettes] A Salute to Swing; Benny Carter, alto saxophone/clarinet; Hank Jones [replaced Teddy Wilson, who was ill], piano; Remo Palmier, guitar; Red Norvo, vibraphone; Louie Bellson, drums; George Duvivier, bass: [for program information, see Tapes (8458:1-2), Box 535]
      12-08-1984: [2 cassettes] Opera A La Carte in Gilbert and Sullivan’s H.M.S. Pinafore: Sullivan, Arthur, 1842-1900. H.M.S. Pinafore
      12-09-1984, 2 p.m.: [2 cassettes] Opera A La Carte in Gilbert and Sullivan’s H.M.S. Pinafore: Sullivan, Arthur, 1842-1900. H.M.S. Pinafore
      12-09-1984, 8 p.m.: [2 cassettes] Opera A La Carte in Gilbert and Sullivan’s H.M.S. Pinafore: Sullivan, Arthur, 1842-1900. H.M.S. Pinafore
      12-11-1984: Pasadena Chamber Orchestra; Robert Duerr, director/conductor; Judith Nelson, soprano; Candice Burrows, mezzo-soprano; William Vannice, countertenor; Mark Bleeke, tenor; Jan Opalach, baritone; Pasadena Chamber Orchestra Chorus: [for program information, see Tapes (8459:1-2), Box 535]
      12-15-1984: Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra(L.A.C.O.); Gerard Schwarz, director/conductor: Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Brandenburgische Konzerte
      01-12-1985: Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra (L.A.C.O.); Gerard Schwarz, director/conductor; Lorin Hollander, piano: Lazarof, Henri. Chamber symphony -- Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Concertos, piano, orchestra, no. 5, op. 103, F major -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Serenades, K. 320, D major
      01-14-1985: [2 cassettes] Young Musicians Foundation Debut Orchestra; Lalo Schifrin, director; Lucas Richman, asst. conductor; Nelson Nirenberg, guest conductor; Daniel Shapiro, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8501:1-2), Box 535]
      01-17-1985: New England Youth Ensemble: [no program available]
      01-20-1985: Andre Watts, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8502:1-2), Box 535]
      01-21-1985: Ben Holt, baritone; Cliff Jackson, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8503:1-2), Box 535]
      01-26-1985: Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra Bach Soloists: Maurita Phillips-Thornburgh, soprano; Marilyn Savage, mezzo-soprano; Paul L. Johnson, tenor; Dale Morich, baritone; Ilkka Talvi, violin; Polly Sweeney, violin; Janet Lakatos, viola; Douglas Davis, cello; Susan Ranney, bass; David Shostac, flute; Allan Vogel, oboe; Kenneth Munday, bassoon; Patricia Mabee, harpsichord: Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Am Abend aber desselbigen Sabbats. Sinfonia -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Liebster Jesu, mein Verlangen. Hier in meines Vaters Stätte -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Schmücke dich, O liebe Seele (Cantata). Ermuntre dich -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Es wartet alles auf dich. Gott versorget alles Leben -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Jesu, der du meine Seele (Cantata). Wir eilen mit schwachen, doch emsigen Schritten -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Hercules auf dem Scheidewege. [Title from program:] Ich bin deine, du bist meine -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Hercules auf dem Scheidewege. Treues Echo -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Also hat Gott die Welt geliebt. Mein gläubiges Herze, frohlokke, sing’, scherze -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Ach Gott, wie manches Herzeleid (Cantata), BWV 58. [Title from program:] Ich hab’ vor mir ein’ schwere Reis’ -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Sonatas, violin, harpsichord, BWV 1015, A major -- Hoffmann, Melchior, ca. 1679-1715. Schlage doch, gewünschte Stunde -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Oster-Oratorium. Sanfte soll mein Todeskummer -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Liebster Jesu, mein Verlangen. Nun verschwinden alle Plagen -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Nach dir, Herr, verlanget mich. [Title from program:] Cedern mussen vo der Winden -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Mache dich, mein Geist, bereit. [Title from program:] Drum so last uns imerdar
      01-28-1985: Steve [Stephen] Hough, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8504:1-2), Box 535]
      02-09-1985: Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra (L.A.C.O.); Gerard Schwarz, director; Vittorio Negri, guest conductor; David Shostac, flute; Allan Vogel, oboe; Paul Shure, violin; Bonnie Douglas, violin; Janet Lakatos, viola; Roland Kato, viola d’amore: Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Concerto ripieno, RV 158 -- Telemann, Georg Philipp, 1681-1767. Concertos, viola, string orchestra, TWV 51:G9, G major -- Albinoni, Tomaso, 1671-1750. Sinfonie e concerti, string orchestra, op. 2. Sonata, no. 6 -- Telemann, Georg Philipp, 1681-1767. Concertos, flute, oboe d'amore, viola d'amore, string orchestra, TWV 53:E1, E major -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Concertos, violins (2), string orchestra, BWV 1043, D minor -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Concerti grossi, violins (2), violoncello, string orchestra, op. 6. No. 10
      02-16-1985: Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra (L.A.C.O.); Gerard Schwarz, director/conductor; Juilliard String Quartet; Marilyn Savage, mezzo-soprano: Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Concerti grossi, violins (2), violoncello, string orchestra, op. 6. No. 7 -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Musikalisches Opfer. Ricercar a 6; arr. -- Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951. Concertos, string quartet, orchestra -- Falla, Manuel de, 1876-1946. Amor brujo. Selections
      02-17-1985: [2 cassettes] Dame Janet Baker, mezzo-soprano; Martin Isepp, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8507:1-2), Box 536]
      03-03-1985: [2 cassettes] Jessye Norman, soprano; Joseph Villa, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8511:1-2), Box 536]
      03-07-1985: [2 cassettes] Royal Philharmonic Orchestra of London; Yehudi Menuhin, conductor; Leland Chen, violin: [for program information, see Tapes (8513:1-2), Box 536]
      03-16-1985: Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra (L.A.C.O.); Gerard Schwarz, director/conductor; Maurice André, trumpet: Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Suites, orchestra, BWV 1069, D major -- Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Concertos, trumpet, orchestra, H. VIIe, 1, E♭ major -- Telemann, Georg Philipp, 1681-1767. Sonatas, trumpet, string orchestra, TWV 44:1, D major -- Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix, 1809-1847. Sommernachtstraum. Selections
      03-21-1985: [2 cassettes] Academy of Ancient Music; Christopher Hogwood, director/harpsichord; Emma Kirkby, soprano; David Thomas, bass; Catherine Mackintosh, violin; Christopher Hirons, violin: [for program information, see Tapes (8518:1-2), Box 537]
      03-23-1985: [2 cassettes; 1 in Box 670] Kathleen Battle, soprano; Lawrence Skrobacs, piano: [see cassette in Box 670]
      Opera A La Carte; Deller Consort; Bellson, Louis; Deller, Mark; Duvivier, George; Baker, Janet; Carter, Benny; Fitzwilliam String Quartet; Chen, Leland; Menuhin, Yehudi, 1916-1999; Villa, Joseph; Norman, Jessye; Negri, Vittorio; Shure, Paul; Mayer, Steven; Hough, Stephen; Juilliard String Quartet; Isepp, Martin; Douglas, Bonnie; Kato, Roland; Battle, Kathleen; Skrobacs, Lawrence; Hirons, Christopher; Thomas, David; André, Maurice; Barbagallo, James; Amadeus String Quartet; Royal Philharmonic Orchestra; Mackintosh, Catherine; Kirkby, Emma; Hogwood, Christopher; Academy of Ancient Music (1973- ); Hollander, Lorin; Schifrin, Lalo; Young Musicians Foundation. Debut Orchestra; Shapiro, Daniel (pianist); Bleeke, Mark; Schwarz, Gerard; Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra; Rodriguez, Santiago; Opalach, Jan; Nelson, Judith; Burrows, Candice; Vannice, William; Pasadena Chamber Orchestra; Duerr, Robert; Shostac, David; Munday, Kenneth; Ranney, Susan; Vogel, Allan; Lakatos, Janet; Davis, Douglas; Mabee, Patricia; Talvi, Ilkka; Holt, Ben; Norvo, Red; Jackson, Cliff; Palmier, Remo; Phillips-Thornburgh, Maurita; Jones, Hank; Morich, Dale; Richman, Lucas; Nirenberg, Nelson; Watts, Andre; New England Youth Ensemble
    - Concert Recordings:, 03-23-1985 -- 10-21-1985; 36 audio cassettes (Box 670)
      03-23-1985: [2 cassettes; 1 in Box 669] Kathleen Battle, soprano; Lawrence Skrobacs, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8519:1-2), Box 537]
      03-30-1985: Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra (L.A.C.O.); Gerard Schwarz, director/conductor; Carol Rosenberger, piano; John Guarnieri, tenor; Paul L. Johnson, tenor; Michael Gallup, bass; Dale Morich, bass: Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Concerti grossi, op. 3. No. 4 -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Concertos, piano, orchestra, K. 595, B♭ major -- Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Baĭka -- Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963. Sinfonietta
      03-31-1985: [2 cassettes] Sergio & Odair Assad, duo-guitarists: [for program information, see Tapes (8520:1-2), Box 537]
      04-15-1985: [2 cassettes] Chantal Juillet, violin, Francine Kay, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8522:1-2), Box 537]
      04-17-1985: [2 cassettes] Narciso Yepes, guitar; Nicanor Zabaleta, harp: [for program information, see Tapes (8523:1-2), Box 537]
      04-18-1985: [2 cassettes] Suk Trio: [for program information, see Tapes (8524:1-2), Box 537]
      04-22-1985: [2 cassettes] Mitsuko Uchida, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8525:1-2), Box 538]
      04-23-1985: Pasadena Chamber Orchestra; Robert Duerr, director/conductor; Michele Zukovsky, clarinet: Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Sinfonia -- Brown, Rayner, 1912-1999. [Title from program:] Concerto for clarinet and orchestra [world premiere] -- Busoni, Ferruccio, 1866-1924. Concertino, clarinet, orchestra, op. 48 -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Symphonies, D. 936 A, D major [American premiere]
      04-25-1985: [2 cassettes] Andre Watts, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8526:1-2), Box 538]
      04-28-1985: Elmar Oliveira, violin; Robert McDonald, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8527:1-2), Box 538]
      05-06-1985: [2 cassettes] American Youth Symphony; Mehli Mehta, director/conductor; Timothy Landauer, cello: [for program information, see Tapes (8529:1-2), Box 538]
      05-08-1985: Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra (L.A.C.O.); Gerard Schwarz, director; Robert Bernhardt, guest conductor; Michala Petri, recorder; Ilkka Talvi, violin: Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Concerti grossi, violins (2), violoncello, string orchestra, op. 6. No. 5 -- Sammartini, Giuseppe, 1695-1750. Concertos, recorder, string orchestra, F major -- Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Concertos, recorder, string orchestra, RV 443, C major -- Tartini, Giuseppe, 1692-1770. Concertos, violin, string orchestra, D. 45, D minor -- Wassenaer, Unico Wilhelm, graaf van, 1692-1766. Concerti armonici. N. 6
      05-09-1985: [2 cassettes] Malcolm Bilson, fortepiano: [for program information, see Tapes (8530:1-2), Box 538]
      05-15-1985: PUSD [Pasadena Unified School District All City Instrumental Music Festival]: [for program information, see Tapes (8531:1-2), Box 538]
      05-23-1985: Pasadena Youth Symphony Orchestra; Donn Laurence Mills, conductor: [for program information, see Tape (8533:1), Box 507]
      05-28-1985: [4 cassettes] Pasadena Chamber Orchestra; Robert Duerr, director/conductor: [no program information available]
      05-29-1985: Pasadena Young Musicians Orchestra: [for program information, see Tapes (8534:1-2), Box 507]
      07-11-1985: [4 cassettes] Blomstedt Institute Symphony Orchestra [Herbert Blomstedt Institute of Orchestra Conducting and Symphonic Performance]: Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Music for the royal fireworks -- Bruckner, Anton, 1824-1896. Symphonies, no. 4, E♭ major. Andante quasi allegretto -- Weber, Carl Maria von, 1786-1826. Concertinos, clarinet, orchestra, op. 26, E♭ major -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Meistersinger von Nürnberg. Vorspiel -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Symphonies, no. 4, op. 60, B♭ major
      10-12-1985: Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra (L.A.C.O.); Gerard Schwarz, director/conductor; Gary Graffman, piano; Lucy Shelton, soprano: Stock, David, 1939- American accents [world premiere] -- Barber, Samuel, 1910-1981. Knoxville, summer of 1915 -- Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953. Concertos, piano, 1 hand, orchestra, op. 53, B♭ major -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Symphonies, no. 1, op. 21, C major
      10-16-1985: [2 cassettes] Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra (L.A.C.O.); Gerard Schwarz, director/conductor; Maurita Phillips-Thornburgh, soprano; Marilyn Savage, mezzo-soprano; Paul L. Johnson, tenor; Dale Morich, bass; the Combined Choirs of the Claremont Colleges, Jon Bailey and Michael Deane Lamkin, directors: Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Masses, BWV 232, B minor
      10-21-1985: Pasadena Chamber Orchestra; Robert Duerr, director/conductor; Janice McVeigh, soprano; Diane Thomas, soprano; Kristor Lawson, countertenor; Robert Tate, tenor; Pasadena Chamber Orchestra Chorus: Schütz, Heinrich, 1585-1672. Psalmen Davids (1619). 100. Psalm -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Concerti grossi, op. 3. No. 3 -- Berg, Alban, 1885-1935. Lyrische Suite. Selections; arr. -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Lobet den Herrn, alle Heiden -- Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. [Title from program:] Contesa delle Stagioni (Serenata)
      Zabaleta, Nicanor; Yepes, Narciso; Uchida, Mitsuko; Sukovo trio; Duerr, Robert; Pasadena Chamber Orchestra; Zukovsky, Michele; Oliveira, Elmar; Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra; Morich, Dale; Gallup, Michael; Guarnieri, John; Kay, Francine; Juillet, Chantal; Assad, Sérgio; Assad, Odair; Bilson, Malcolm; Mills, Donn; Blomstedt, Herbert; Graffman, Gary; Phillips-Thornburgh, Maurita; Schwarz, Gerard; Shelton, Lucy; Rosenberger, Carol; Battle, Kathleen; Thomas, Diane, singer; Skrobacs, Lawrence; McDonald, Robert; Watts, Andre; American Youth Symphony; Landauer, Timothy; Petri, Michala; Mehta, Mehli; Talvi, Ilkka; Bernhardt, Robert
    - Concert Recordings:, 10-22-1985 -- 02-24-1986; 36 audio cassettes (Box 671)
      10-22-1985: [Recreation of] Paul Whiteman’s Historic Aeolian Hall Concert; Maurice Peress, conductor; Ivan Davis and Dick Hyman, pianos: [for program information, see Tapes (8541:1-2), Box 539; see also Tapes (8540:1-2), Box 539]
      10-23-1985: [2 cassettes] [Recreation of] Paul Whiteman’s Historic Aeolian Hall Concert; Maurice Peress, conductor; Ivan Davis and Dick Hyman, pianos: [for program information, see Tapes (8541:1-2), Box 539]
      10-24-1985: [2 cassettes] Oscar Peterson, piano: [no program listed, see also Tapes (8542:1-2), Box 539]
      10-26-1985: [2 cassettes] Vienna Chamber Ensemble; Gerhart Hetzel, director/first violin: [for program information, see Tapes (8543:1-2), Box 539]
      10-27-1985: [2 cassettes] Bella Davidovich, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8544:1-2), Box 539]
      11-12-1985: Pasadena Chamber Orchestra; Robert Duerr, director/conductor; Mayumi Ohira, violin; Roland Kato, viola: Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Instrumental miniatures -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Sinfonie concertanti, violin, viola, orchestra, K. 364, E♭ major -- Dion, Denis, 1957- Veuillez agréger les sentiments mes plus distincts [American premiere] -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Symphonies, K. 550, G minor
      11-16-1985: [2 cassettes] Clancy Brothers & Tommy Makem: [no program listed; see also Tapes (8546:1-2), Box 540]
      11-17-1985: Clancy Brothers & Tommy Makem: [no program listed; see also Tapes (8547:1-2), Box 540]
      11-19-1985: [2 cassettes] London Early Music Group; James Tyler, director/lute/baroque guitar: [for program information, see Tapes (8548:1-2), Box 540]
      11-20-1985: Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra Bach Soloists; Maurita Phillips-Thornburgh, soprano; Marilyn Savage, mezzo-soprano; Paul L. Johnson, tenor; Dale Morich, baritone; Ilkka Talvi, violin; Polly Sweeney, violin; Roland Kato, viola; Michael Mathews, cello; David Young, bass; David Shostac, flute; Susan Greenberg, flute; Allan Vogel, oboe; Patricia Mabee, harpsichord: Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Ich hatte viel Bekümmernis. Sinfonia -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Ich hatte viel Bekümmernis. [Title from program:] Bache von gesalz ‘nen Zahren -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Süsser Trost, mein Jesus kömmt. Süsser Trost, mein Jesus kömmt -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Friede sei mit dir. Welt, ade! ich bin dein müde -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Erwünschtes Freudenlicht. [Title from program:] Gesegnete Christen, gluckselige Herde -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Erforsche mich, Gott, und erfahre mein Herz. [Title from program] Uns treffen zwar der Sunden Flecken -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. O ewiges Feuer, o Ursprung der Liebe, BWV 34. [Title from program:] Wohl euch, ihr auserwahlten Seelen -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Sehet, wir geh’n hinauf gen Jerusalem. Es ist vollbracht -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Wo soll ich fliehen hin (Cantata). [Title from program:] Ergiesse dich reichlich, du gottlich Quelle -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Mache dich, mein Geist, bereit. [Title from program:] Opening chorus -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Sonatas, flute, continuo, BWV 1033, C major -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Weichet nur, betrübte Schatten. Weichet nur, betrübte Schatten -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Christus, der ist mein Leben (Cantata). [Title from program:] Ach! schlage doch bald -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Liebster Gott, wenn werd ich sterben. Doch weichet, ihr tollen vergeblichen Sorgen -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Lobe den Herren, den mächtigen König der Ehren. Lobe den Herren -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Was Gott tut, das ist wohlgetan (Cantata), BWV 99. Was Gott tut, das ist wohlgetan (Chorus)
      11-26-1985: Dukes of Dixieland: [for program information, see Tapes (8550:1-2), Box 540; see also Tapes (8549:1-2), Box 540]
      01-18-1986: L.A. Vocal Arts Ensemble; Armen Guzelimian, artistic director/piano; Delcina Stevenson, soprano; Darlene Romano, soprano; Janet Smith, mezzo-soprano; Rickie Weiner-Gole, mezzo-soprano; Paul Johnson, tenor; Jeffrey Araluce, tenor; Dale Morich, baritone; Michael Gallup, bass; Raul Herrera, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8601:1-2), Box 540]
      01-20-1986: [2 cassettes] Marc-André Hamelin, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8602:1-2), Box 541]
      01-27-1986 [01-28-1986?]: [Dr. Herbert] Zipper [children’s] program: [no program available; see Tape (8605:1), Box 541]
      01-27-1986: [3 cassettes, 1 dated incorrectly] Timothy Landauer, cello; Doris Stevenson, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8604:1-2), Box 541]
      01-30-1986: [2 cassettes] Walter Klien, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8606:1-2), Box 541]
      02-03-1986: Christopher Trakas, baritone; Steven Blier, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8607:1-2), Box 541]
      02-16-1986: [2 cassettes] Marian McPartland Duo [Trio]: [for program information, see Tapes (8608:1-2), Box 541]
      02-19-1986: Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra (L.A.C.O.); Gerard Schwarz, director; Kenneth Jean, guest conductor; Paul Esswood, countertenor: Purcell, Henry, 1659-1695. Gordian knot unty’d -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Concerti grossi, violins (2), violoncello, string orchestra, op. 6. No. 11 -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Widerstehe doch der Sünde. Selections -- Bach, Johann Christoph, 1642-1703. Ach, dass ich Wassers gnug hätte -- Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Stabat Mater, RV 621, F minor -- Bach, Carl Philipp Emanuel, 1714-1788. Symphonies, string orchestra, H. 661, B minor
      02-24-1986: [2 cassettes] David Buechner, piano: [for program information, see Tapes (8611:1-2), Box 541]